(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-20T00:51:59.359876",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.7-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Greetings Cece, my fated rival!
Greetings Ina, my destined rival!
And hello to ev—
...anyone watching from...
Serendipity!
Woo!
Remember, if you want a chance for your wish to be featured on the Otomo or the Takodachi that we made,
post about it with #WishUponTakoTomo!
Yay! Thank you AmiAmi for supporting our rivalry!
And for supporting Serendipity! Be sure to check out their booth at...
Anime Expo!
Yay!
Hey pebbles!
It's Koseki Bijou!
:D :D
And all of hololive BASE is here with me!
All 14 of us!
hololive BASE is coming to Round 1 USA locations nationwide,
starting this September!
Come hang out with us!
Follow @round1usa on Instagram and X so you don't miss out on any updates!
We can't wait to see you there!
Bye-bye!
A-D-V-E-N-T
Everyone, let's light the fire!
Time to get this party started!
Fire, fire, light the fire
Brighter, higher, as you desire
Chasing all that we aspire
Spreading out like wildfire
Never ever, have I ever
Been a sinner, been a dreamer
Take the chance and with my lighter
Start the fire
Come pull me out
I'm out of sheep to count
This overkill of sad old stories wearing me down
Snap out of the system
Break out, give it everything
This is our time
We're yours to discover
Hello, brand new world
Would you welcome the light?
And free us from the night
Fire, fire, light the fire
Brighter, higher, as you desire
Ignite our beating hearts
Dance into the flame of life
新しい世界へ
To a brand new world
Dance until the end of time
異次元の向こう側 連れてってあげる
I'll take you beyond different dimensions
Rebellion
I know that I can still be
The future of this story
I know that I can be free
The one and the only
They tell me that I'm crazy
I'll never let them stop me
With this,
our advent begins!
Time to get this party started!
Never ever, have I ever
Been a sinner, been a dreamer
Fire, fire, light the fire
Ignite these beating hearts
Jump into the stream of life
新しい世界へ
To a brand new world
Jump until the end of time
異次元の向こう側 連れてってあげる
I'll take you beyond different dimensions
Dance into the flame of life
それぞれの聖地へ
To our respective sacred lands
Dance until the end of time
奇跡の向こう側 連れてってあげる
I'll take you beyond miracles
Rebellion
Time to get this party started!
Fire, fire, light the fire
Brighter, higher, as you desire
Time to get this party started!
Don't, don't know me, unpredictable
Takin' you all below, takin' you all be-
Don't, don't know me, irresistible
Takin' you all below, be-be-below we go
They think they want it, huh?
They wanna get-get some
Then we'll take them down, down, down, down
Way down in the borderline, run, it's no surprise
You ain't gonna win, but you can try
Hey, I told you you would know, and end up in my lineup
Listen, listen
Run or hide and scream out, already locked you up!
Those games you always play
Call me, cover-up, won't hear anything
A name is signed out right on your heart
Throwing the keys out just tonight-ight-ight
Drop! Lock that! Lock that! Pop that lock!
Drop! Lock that! No way to just forget, get that lock!
The higher I rise, the further you drop
Standing on the...
Edge! Don't know me, unpredictable, tip you over the edge
Think you know where to go
Show you something real on my level, no, you'll never know, reverse also
この場所なら
If it's this place
Woo! Oh! Hey, we got it! Hey!
Run in the light, oh mio Dio
Run in the light, oh my God
What's wrong, what's right?
Crashing in a fantasy, wanna be diseased
Show that you will never make it out
I swallow now, and do it, do it
稲妻 lightning in now, now, and the music got a lockdown, oh
Inazuma lightning in now, now, and the music got a lockdown, oh
Seeing your guilty heart
We're not gonna stop, it's just started
Done!
Oh...
Get down, get down, let it drop
Run it like that, run it like that
Get down, get down, down, down, down
Takin' you u-u-up, let's go
Takin' you be-be-below
Told you already, no, don't chance, and we know it
Run in the light, oh mio Dio
Run in the light, oh my God
What's wrong, what's right with you?
Run in the night, oh mio Dio
Run in the night, oh my God
Come take a bite
Never-ending endless...
Drop! Lock that, lock that, pop that lock, lock that!
Not one to just forget
(Get, get that)
We rise...
The higher I rise, down further you dive
The higher I rise, the further down you dive!
Standin' on the edge
Standing on the edge,
Don't know me, unpredictable, typical you
Got nowhere to go
Show you somethin' real, my
show you something real, my
Level, no, you'll never know, as above, so
Below, you should know (So let's go!)
Just a little unpredictable, beautiful, just the start
Let's get 'em, let's get 'em, baby, go!
Next level, almost criminal
As above, so it goes below
준비?
Ready?
That's cooking, what a shame
Players, they all complain
와인이 넘쳐나게 and shout out loud, ta-da!
Let the wine overflow and shout out loud, ta-da!
But ain't got time so dry those eyes
Look around, what satisfies
The broken and bruised?
I got something to prove now
Abracadabra, let's go
Watch them like dishes, they fall (Shake, shake)
끝까지 가보자고
Let's go all the way,
난 음악에 취해
I'm drunk on the music.
Trouble, more trouble, we love it to ladder we do
Or die
We hit that high!
(Snake eyes, snake eyes)
Come on now, don't be shy
두껍게 달라붙어
Stick closely to it,
물자 all day, all night
bite down all day, all night.
So turn it up!
Can't stop, won't stop preaching
Who said the sky's the limit? Show them that we mean business
We are the young ambitious
Snake eyes, they never lie
Fly high with pride and leave all peace behind!
지금 우리들은 광란의 party
Right now, we're at a raving party,
다 열자 개판 safari
let's open it up, a chaotic safari.
Baddie, baddie, nobody can stop me, goodie, goodie, pull up
Go, go, go, baller
Acting on artists, that boss, more jollier, multi-slacker
Shake it off, what goes around
Shoot your mouth, we'll come back down
Ready the fight
Ready the screaming!
Abracadabra, let's go
Watch it, we're ripping it up!
걱정은 안 해도 돼
No need to worry,
다 털어 털어 devil of play
shake it all off, devil of play.
Freeze it up, demon
Believe in the beat and just wait and see
We hit that high!
(Snake eyes, snake eyes)
Come on now, don't be shy
두껍게 달라붙어
Stick closely to it,
물자 all day, all night
bite down all day, all night.
Let me hear you alive!
Let the beat drop!
Go!
We go hard!
(Go hard!)
Get down with that drum, whatever, let's go!
We go hard!
I want it all!
끝이 나쁘건 어쨌건
Whether the ending is bad or whatever,
죽지 않아 전부 골라
I won't die, pick them all.
맞서 싸워 시작이야
Stand and fight, it's just beginning,
끝까지 다뤄 가
take control until the end.
We hit that high!
(Snake eyes, snake eyes)
Come on now, don't be shy
같이 좀 놀아봐 이렇게
Come play with me like this,
멈출 수 없어 같이 다 타네
can't stop, we're all burning up together.
Don't be afraid of losing
It's just a new beginning
Look at the clouds we dealing
Sometimes it takes a villain
Thank God the time is nigh
Fly high with pride and leave all peace behind!
Cauterize the ties
This ain't the only battlefield that can televise
Ego is enormous, so put the camera down and face it
They went and got complacent
Kill and run with me
You say it's death and nothing no one else can relate
Just know the company you keep is in the business of hate, are you...
Afraid, run away,
I'm close to getting mine.
I've been dancing on my own in a bulletproof vest,
Go and shoot, shoot, shoot out, baby, doesn't matter.
Ricochet, ricochet, you can think about me anytime, anytime.
So get your street fight, this a trench war,
I'll make you march, march, march till you hit the floor.
Getting thirsty for collision, let them wonder what they're missing in the front brawl.
Now here we go!
Can't you hear? We see no white line,
It's the call to arms.
Become the prison, be unforgiven, make the decision.
Catch you looking for permission to riot? You got it wrong.
Think about it, your identity clicks on, now hear the roar.
Stand for nothing, play the coward, stare at someone you devour,
It's the set-in twisted masquerade's existence!
Demand us to hate this! Wow!
邪魔残す気？ この子に決めた
Intending to leave obstacles? I chose this one,
角度を調整 角度微調整
adjusting the angle, fine-tuning the angle.
I could tell the boy gotta please anybody, decide who is special and discard the rest.
Gambler by nature, chips start to stack,
Waste your money on some loser, crap.
才能？ 才能？ 抱き付いて足掻いた
Talent? Talent? Clung to it and struggled,
集まったの後悔
full of gathered regrets.
Defeat the following, starving 時間の無駄無駄や
Defeat the following, starving, it's just a waste of time.
Yeah, yeah, I could tell you're not a friend.
あー、せーので、顔持ち、食い散らかせ
Ah, on the count of three, hold your face and tear it apart,
足んないくらいさ 歌舞伎町でも成りさ
it's not even enough, even Kabukicho will do.
舞台客のlonely lonely 多分ほら急いでおいでよ
Stage audience's lonely, lonely, hey, hurry on over,
止めてあげるから 誰も登ってみ下してよ
'cause I'll stop you—someone climb up and look down on them.
Hey war, in war, hey war, whoa...
In war, in war, hey war, whoa...
Say yeah!
Hey war, in war, hey war, whoa...
In war, in war, hey war, whoa...
Ah!
才能？ 才能？ 抱き付き絡まった
Talent? Talent? Clinging and getting entangled,
ガンディレクターにすり抜け See this?
slipping past the gun director, see this?
Back down, breakdown, cursing when you're out of reaction,
Shut it, shut it! I'm the one that's not impressed.
てめえのせいで 咲き乱れ 鳥肌
Because of you, blooming in madness, goosebumps,
パッと 怒鳴り 鳴り響く ワァァ...
suddenly shouting, echoing loudly, whoa...
We're not rivals!
We're not equals!
I gotta tell you,
I never liked you.
Nor would I, why die here? Let me ignite you.
Break through, take take control,
Fight fire always, simple to endure.
It's a story you're trapped to like me, like you overestimated every word I told.
Take a name but it doesn't make a difference to shout,
I got a million different enemies I cannot recount.
You fucked up, do a battle when you know that you fall,
Kill the motive, bitch, watch it all burn!
I gotta tell you,
I never liked you.
Nor would I, why die here? Let me ignite you.
When thunder crashes down,
When the world drips under my pressure,
There'll be no one to save you.
Where is your passion, human will to survive?
Was it just empty words for your dream?
I reach inside this sound,
Now what the, what remains is illusion and danger,
'Cause of you, wanted it this way.
We're not rivals!
We're not equals!
Lately I realize I would never be, never be alone,
It was always right in front of me.
Do you know, do you remember, remember
How we used to be so carefree?
Oh, hey, I can feel...
...the rain wash over
us, yeah
Can you hear my heart like thunder?
Upside down 떨리는 내 목소리
Upside down, my trembling voice
I've got to make a move, make a move
So far I could not break through the cage I'm in
I don't know how to reach for you
Hardly ever get a chance to speak alone
Could it ever be, can't you feel it too
Side by side, we could laugh all through our days
Baby, just let me make my way to you
Can't make them stop, hidden sparks inside ignite and flare up
And when we talk, all my secrets spilling over the top
So when I step up to your side and my heart is beating in double time
And every moment, you make me feel alive, it goes like
I can feel the rain wash over
us, yeah
Can you hear my heart like thunder?
Upside down 떨리는 내 목소리
Upside down, my trembling voice
I've got to make a move, make a move
So far I could not break through the cage I'm in
I don't know how to reach for you
Hardly ever get a chance to speak alone
Could it ever be, can't you feel it too
Side by side, we could laugh all through our days
Baby, just let me make my way to you
Hardly ever get a chance to speak alone
Could it ever be, can't you feel it too
Side by side, we could laugh all through our days
Baby, just let me make my way to you
Hello! Hello!
Oi, oi, oi!
Hello, hello, hello, hello, hello!
Hello! High and low!
Hello up there!
Hello down there!
Hello, 皆!
Hello, everyone!
Hey, who are you?
Hiya, darlings! This is hololive English -Advent-'s devilish diva...
...the one, the only, Nerissa Ravencroft!
And with me...
Ah~
Roses are red, the fire of my heart is blue,
also known as the Scarlet Queen, the harbinger of order, leader...
...of Justice!
I am Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame!
Lovely to see, to see you!
Lovely!
As thou art! / Yeah!
Wow, what a setlist thus far, huh?
I know! We're starting off really strong!
We had...
Sneaking! Sneaking! / Sneaker! Sneaker! Yeah!
Woah, oh my god.
And we had Mori rocking it out!
Seriously!
And then Kronii coming in with her new song, so good!
Yeah, such cute dance moves!
And we had Advent and Justice, of course!
Yes, yes. Did you enjoy?
Did you enjoy?
I can't hear you, did you enjoy?
Yeah, hello? Is it good so far?
Well, you know what, we didn't have solos yesterday.
No, no. So we must be having them today, right?
So excited!
Oh, yeah, for mine, I want to practice something, okay?
Oh, okay. Go on.
A little chant from Great Exardia.
So when I go "Oggy, oggy, oggy", you go "Oi, oi, oi!"
Are you ready?
Okay! Here we go!
Oggy, oggy, oggy!
Oi, oi, oi!
Perfect! 完璧!
Perfect! Flawless!
完璧, yes!
Flawless, yes!
What about you? Any sneak peeks about your solo?
Mmm, would you guys really like a sneak peek?
Well, uh, I think I have to remind you all...
...no matter how you identify, no matter what you are,
you in this audience today...
...are my wives! Can I hear it from my wives?!
What the freak! Everyone here is your waifu?!
Yeah! Including you!
What?! Uh...
So, if I ask you to sing along, you have to, all right?
You gotta.
Um, yeah, that's my hint.
Did that give it away? Maybe a little.
Nice, nice, nice!
You know, we're singing, and I was thinking that...
...to hear you guys sing, too.
You guys know I like harmonies.
Yes!
So we're gonna split you into different notes, okay?
Yes.
So we have you guys over here...
You guys over here...
And all of you at the top!
So, we're gonna start off with you guys here.
Yeah. We want you to hold this note.
Ah...
Perfect!
You guys: Ah...
Up there: Ah...
All right, everyone together!
Ah, ah, ah, ah...
Woo! Beautiful! Beautiful!
Oh my gosh, we have our own choir!
So good!
We're gonna do that more often, that was cool!
Yeah! I like hearing you all sing for us.
Ah... Hey, that reminds me of a song, doesn't it? You know that first note?
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
You know, something like...
Three, two, one...
It's wondrous,
somehow we met along the way!
Now here you are beside me,
embracing serendipity!
Wow, that was great, wasn't it?
Yeah!
Harmonizing... Ah...
It's wonderful harmonizing with you.
And I just want to say thank you so much for being my friend.
I love you!
Ahhh!
Anyway... We gotta sing together.
We're gonna sing together!
I got too excited! I got too excited!
I'm just too happy.
I'm so happy, too!
Whew, whew, whew!
Whew, you go whew, whew, whew.
Ah, I spammed too fast. There we go.
Whew. Anyway...
無料配信は次の曲で最後になります！
The free stream will end with the next song!
ライブの続きはぜひ配信チケットを買って見てね！
Be sure to buy a stream ticket to watch the rest of the live concert!
The YouTube free sneak peek is only until the next song, which is a duet.
If you want to continue watching, click the link in the description and get your tickets now!
All right, everybody.
After three, we all say Serendipity, got it?
Yeah.
Aw, thanks so very much! We love you guys so much!
We love you! Mwah!
All right, here we go!
Yes! Three, two, one, Serendipity!
Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame
Nerissa Ravencroft
Bloodraven
残酷な天使のように
Like a cruel angel,
少年よ 神話になれ
Young boy, become a legend!
蒼い風がいま 胸のドアを叩いても
Even if the blue wind knocks on the door to your heart right now,
私だけをただ見つめて 微笑んでるあなた
You just gaze only at me, smiling.
そっとふれるもの もとめることに夢中で
Yearning and reaching out to softly touch things,
運命さえまだ知らない いたいけな瞳
With innocent eyes that know not of destiny yet.
だけどいつか気付くでしょう その背中には
But one day, you will surely realize that upon your back,
遥か未来 めざすための 羽根があること
You have wings meant to soar toward the distant future.
残酷な天使のテーゼ 窓辺からやがて飛び立つ
A cruel angel's thesis will soon take flight from the window.
ほとばしる熱いパトスで 思い出を裏切るなら
With a surging, fiery pathos, if you were to betray your memories...
この空を抱いて輝く
Embrace the skies and shine bright,
少年よ 神話になれ
young boy, become a legend!
蒼い風が今
Even if a blue breeze now
胸のドアを叩いても
knocks upon the door to your heart,
私だけをただ見つめて...
you just gaze only at me...
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
It's your turn, Los Angeles!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
Back to you, Princess!
ずっと眠ってる 私の愛の揺りかご
Resting asleep forever in the cradle of my love,
あなただけが 夢の使者に呼ばれる朝がくる
the morning comes when only you will be summoned by the messenger of dreams.
細い首筋を 月あかりが映してる
The moonlight reflects upon your slender neck.
世界中の時を止めて 閉じこめたいけど
I want to stop time all across the world and trap it here, but...
もしもふたり逢えたことに意味があるなら
If there is meaning to the two of us meeting,
私はそう 自由を知るためのバイブル
then I am a bible for you to know freedom.
残酷な天使のテーゼ 悲しみがそして始まる
Like a cruel angel's thesis, and so sadness begins.
抱きしめた命のかたち その夢に目覚めたとき
When you awaken to the dream of the form of life you held,
誰よりも光を放つ 少年よ 神話になれ
young boy, shine brighter than anyone else and become a legend!
人は愛をつむぎながら 歴史をつくる
While weaving love, humankind creates history.
女神なんてなれないまま 私は生きる
Unable to become a goddess, I live on.
残酷な天使のテーゼ 窓辺からやがて飛び立つ
Like a cruel angel's thesis, you will soon take flight from the window.
ほとばしる熱いパトスで 思い出を裏切るなら
If you betray memories with overflowing burning pathos,
この空を抱いて輝く 少年よ 神話になれ
embrace the skies and shine bright, young boy, become a legend!
無料パートは終了いたしました。ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching!